https://zenbiotic.com/privacy-policy

Cart
( 0 items $0.00 )
Recently added item(s)
×
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Search:
Search
Foundation EssentialsCleansingOxygenationHydrationNutritionSun & BodyHolistic Lifestyle
Home
/
Privacy Policy, Zenbiotic
Security and Privacy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Zenbiotic collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://www.zenbiotic.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Zenbiotic.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site.Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
Zenbiotic may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
To run and operate our SiteWe may need your information to display content on the Site correctly.
To send periodic emailsWe may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.
We may share or sell information with third parties for marketing or other purposes.
Sharing your personal information
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Zenbiotic collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://www.zenbiotic.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Zenbiotic.
Personal identification information
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site.Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.
Non-personal identification information
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.
Web browser cookies
Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.
How we use collected information
Zenbiotic may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:
To run and operate our SiteWe may need your information to display content on the Site correctly.
To send periodic emailsWe may use the email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests.
How we protect your information
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.
Sharing your personal information
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.
We may share or sell information with third parties for marketing or other purposes.
Electronic newsletters
If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.
Compliance with children's online privacy protection act
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.
Changes to this privacy policy
Zenbiotic has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.
Your acceptance of these terms
By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us.
This document was last updated on October 06, 2015
Exclusive offers for facebook friends
keep updated with the latest offers
Loyalty Point Program
SAVE! Earn loyalty rewards & use points to purchase items.
Register/Sign IN
PRODUCTS
Foundation Essentials Cleansing Oxygenation Hydration NutritionGift Certificates Gift Bag
ABOUT ZENBIOTIC
The Zenbiotic Difference Skin Care Facts & Myths What to expect TestimonialsFAQ's
Return / Shipping Policies Customer Service Press
Secure Payment Methods
Catch the latest news:
Sign up with our newsletter to receive the latest news and offers and receive 15% on your next order!
Would you like to sell Zenbiotic in your spa or store? Or maybe just share us with your friends and online customers? Apply here for a wholesale or affiliate/agent account:
Click here to open account
© 2015 Zenbiotic Skin Care. All Rights Reserved.  |Privacy Policy | Terms and Conditions | 100% Safe shopping | SiteMap
